Hello! Bold Italic Underline Strikethrough
Hey Alice! This is important!
Notice the yellow background note
This cue has 漢字kanji and 東京Tokyo for ruby testing
Speaker styling with classes and combined styles
Testing multiple cues with underline and colors
Right-aligned cue with strikethrough and bold
This cue demonstrates automatic line positioning and center alignment
Mixing everything: bold italic underline strike highlight 日hi
Left-aligned with class styling
and important cue
Right-aligned, multiple cues, ruby:
漢kan 字ji
End of feature test: bold, italic, underline, strikethrough, note, 東京Tokyo